import { TopicData } from '../types/types';

const europeanCuntriesData: TopicData[] = [
  {
    front: '🇮🇪',
    back: 'Ireland',
  },
  {
    front: '🇮🇹',
    back: 'Italy',
  },
  {
    front: '🇩🇪',
    back: 'Germany',
  },
  {
    front: '🏴󠁧󠁢󠁥󠁮󠁧󠁿',
    back: 'England',
  },
  {
    front: '🏴󠁧󠁢󠁳󠁣󠁴󠁿',
    back: 'Scotland',
  },
  {
    front: '🏴󠁧󠁢󠁷󠁬󠁳󠁿',
    back: 'Wales',
  },
  {
    front: '🇫🇷',
    back: 'France',
  },
  {
    front: '🇳🇱',
    back: 'Netherlands',
  },
  {
    front: '🇨🇭',
    back: 'Switzerland',
  },
  {
    front: '🇬🇷',
    back: 'Greece',
  },
  {
    front: '🇵🇱',
    back: 'Poland',
  },
  {
    front: '🇺🇦',
    back: 'Ukraine',
  },
  {
    front: '',
    back: 'Austria',
  },
  {
    front: '🇧🇪',
    back: 'Belgium',
  },
  {
    front: '🇸🇪',
    back: 'Sweden',
  },
  {
    front: '🇭🇷',
    back: 'Croatia',
  },
  {
    front: '🇳🇴',
    back: 'Norway',
  },
  {
    front: '🇩🇰',
    back: 'Denmark',
  },
  {
    front: '🇦🇱',
    back: 'Albania',
  },
  {
    front: '🇷🇴',
    back: 'Ramania',
  },
  {
    front: '🇲🇹',
    back: 'Malta',
  },
  {
    front: '🇮🇸',
    back: 'Iceland',
  },
  {
    front: '🇫🇮',
    back: 'Finland',
  },
  {
    front: '🇷🇸',
    back: 'Serbia',
  },
  {
    front: '🇨🇿',
    back: 'Czechia',
  },
  {
    front: '🇭🇺',
    back: 'Hungary',
  },
  {
    front: '🇸🇮',
    back: 'Slovenia',
  },
  {
    front: '🇧🇬',
    back: 'Bulgaria',
  },
  {
    front: '🇸🇮',
    back: 'Slovenia',
  },
  {
    front: '🇱🇺',
    back: 'Luxembourg',
  },
  {
    front: '🇨🇾',
    back: 'Cyprus',
  },
  {
    front: '🇲🇪',
    back: 'Montenegro',
  },
  {
    front: '🇪🇪',
    back: 'Estonia',
  },
  {
    front: '🇱🇹',
    back: 'Lithuania',
  },
  {
    front: '🇽🇰',
    back: 'Kosovo',
  },
  {
    front: '🇸🇰',
    back: 'Slovakia',
  },
  {
    front: '🇱🇻',
    back: 'Latvia',
  },
  {
    front: '🇱🇮',
    back: 'Liechtenstein',
  },
  {
    front: '🇧🇾',
    back: 'Belarus',
  },
  {
    front: '🇧🇦',
    back: 'Bosnia and Herzegovina',
  },
  {
    front: '🇲🇰',
    back: 'North Macedonia',
  },
  {
    front: '🇻🇦',
    back: 'Vatican City',
  },
  {
    front: '🇲🇨',
    back: 'Monaco',
  },
  {
    front: '🇲🇩',
    back: 'Moldova',
  },
  {
    front: '🇦🇩',
    back: 'Andorra',
  },
  {
    front: '🇮🇲',
    back: 'Isle of Man',
  },
  {
    front: '🇬🇮',
    back: 'Gibraltar',
  },
  {
    front: '🇯🇪',
    back: 'Jersey',
  },
  {
    front: '🇸🇲',
    back: 'San Marino',
  },
  {
    front: '🇦🇽',
    back: 'Åland Islands',
  },
  {
    front: '🇫🇴',
    back: 'Faroe Islands',
  },
  {
    front: '🇬🇮',
    back: 'Gibraltar',
  },
  {
    front: '🇬🇮',
    back: 'Gibraltar',
  },
  {
    front: '🇬🇮',
    back: 'Gibraltar',
  },
  {
    front: '🇬🇮',
    back: 'Gibraltar',
  },
  {
    front: '🇬🇮',
    back: 'Gibraltar',
  },
  {
    front: '🇬🇮',
    back: 'Gibraltar',
  },
  {
    front: '🇬🇮',
    back: 'Gibraltar',
  },
  {
    front: '🇬🇮',
    back: 'Gibraltar',
  },
];

export { europeanCuntriesData };
